<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FYPCoeliac</string>

    <string name="search_field">Enter product name</string>

    <string name="app_title">Coeliac Scanner</string>
    <!-- Section titles -->
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="coeliac_info">Coeliac Disease</string>
    <string name="gf_diet">Gluten Free Diet</string>
    <string name="labelling_info">Labelling</string>
    <string name="gf_oats">Gluten Free Oats</string>
    <string name="disclaimer">Disclaimer</string>

    <!-- Toolbar titles when navigation menu item is selected -->
    <string-array name="nav_item_activity_titles">
        <item>Gluten Free Diet</item>
        <item>Coeliac Disease</item>
        <item>Labelling</item>
        <item>Gluten Free Oats</item>
        <item>Disclaimer</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Info pages text -->
    <string name="gf_diet_info">There are many reasons for following a gluten free diet, including:\n
        \n•\tCoeliac disease\n•\tNon-coeliac gluten sensitivity \n•\tWheat or gluten allergy\n•\tIrritable
        Bowel Syndrome\n•\tAutoimmune diseases, including rheumatoid arthritis
        and multiple sclerosis\n•\tPersonal choice\n\nGluten is a protein found in wheat, barley, and rye.\n</string>
    <string name="coeliac_info_text">Coeliac disease is an auto-immune disease causing a reaction to
        gluten, a protein found in wheat, barley and rye. Sufferers react abnormally to ingesting
        gluten, causing the intestine to become inflamed and damaged.\n\nSymptoms may include:
        \n•\tDiarrhoea\n•\tConstipation\n•\tBloating\n•\tChronic fatigue\n•\tAnaemia\n•\tFailure
        to thrive in children\n•\tWeight loss\n•\tMouth ulcers\n•\tDepression\n•\tInfertility\n
        \nPresentation of the disease varies from patient to patient, and some may present no symptoms
        at all.\n\nDiagnosis of coeliac disease requires a blood test, followed by an intestinal
        biopsy during a gastroscopy. It is possible for a blood test to give a false negative.\n\n
        The only treatment for coeliac disease is a lifelong gluten free diet.</string>
    <string name="labelling_info_text">A “gluten free” label on food indicates that the product
        contains less than 20 parts per million of gluten. This is a level deemed safe for coeliacs
        to consume.\n\nThe Crossed Grain is an internationally recognised symbol that identifies a
        food product as being gluten free.\n\nWhen checking ingredients lists, it is important to
        check for many hidden and obvious sources of gluten:\n•\tWheat, and any derivatives\n•\tRye
        \n•\tBarley\n•\tOats\n•\tSpelt\n•\tMalt, and any derivatives (excluding Malt Vinegar)\n
        \nIf a product “may contain” any of the above ingredients, coeliacs are advised not to consume them.\n
        \nThe most up-to-date information about what a food contains will always be found on its label.
        While the food list aims to keep an accurate listing of gluten free products, ingredients may
        change before the list can be updated. Therefore, coeliacs are always advised to check the
        label of any food products before they consume it.</string>
    <string name="gf_oats_info_text">Oats do not contain gluten but may be contaminated by gluten
        containing grains during processing. Coeliacs should only consume oats that are labelled
        gluten free.\n\nA minority of coeliacs are still unable to tolerate gluten free oats and so
        must exclude them from their diet.</string>
    <string name="disclaimer_text">The information provided in this application is as up-to-date as
        possible, but the most up-to-date information will always be found on a product’s ingredients
        label. Always check the label of a food product before consuming it.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main_navdrawer">main_navdrawer</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
